rednano.sg 2008-12-17

# Rednano - Singapore's First Local Search & Directory Engine

Privacy Policy

[SPH Search Pte Ltd](http://www.sphsearch.sg/) ("[rednano.sg](http://www.rednano.sg/)") collects information from users for a number of reasons. 

Please read carefully our policy below on data collection and use of the data collected. This policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and/or operated by SPH Search. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various sites or services.

We may amend this policy from time to time, and we will post any such amended policies on this page.  

**_When is information collected from you?_**

  * When you register for any of [SPH Search'](http://www.sphsearch.sg/)s services on websites owned and/or operated by [SPH Search](http://www.sphsearch.sg/), when you take part in any contest, survey or promotion conducted by [SPH Search](http://www.sphsearch.sg/) and/or its business partners and/or when you register as a member of websites hosted by [SPH Search](http://www.sphsearch.sg/) on behalf of its business partners, we may ask you for personal information (including, without limitation, your name, email address, account password, gender, phone number, physical address, occupation, preferences, photos, etc.). We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other [SPH Search](http://www.sphsearch.sg/) services or third parties, or publicly available information. 
  * We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to SPH Search in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 
  * When you visit [SPH Search](http://www.sphsearch.sg/)’s websites or websites hosted by [SPH Search](http://www.sphsearch.sg/) on behalf of its business partners, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 
  * We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. 

**_What is the information used for?_**

  * To provide goods and services by [SPH Search](http://www.sphsearch.sg/) or its designated representatives and/or business partners to you or parties designated by you and matters ancillary thereto.
  * To verify and process payment when you purchase goods and services from our sites.
  * For verification and record of your personal particulars, including comparing it with information from other sources, and using the information to communicate with you.
  * To conduct statistical analysis of the users of our sites, including the number of users, the frequency of use, profile of users, and using such analysis for our business plans, the enhancement of our products and services, targeted advertisements and conveying such information in broad terms (but not information in relation to specific individuals) to third parties who have or propose to have business dealings with us.
  * To send you information, promotions and updates including marketing and advertising materials in relation to our goods and services and those of third party organizations selected by us.
  * To comply with any order of court or directive from authorities investigating any alleged offence, misdeeds and/or abuse or for the purposes of taking legal action against any users for breach of the Terms of Service.
  * For the above purposes by third parties (who may be based outside Singapore) who offer goods and services or sponsor contests or other promotional programs on our sites, whether in conjunction with us or not, if you purchase such goods, use such services or participate in such contests and promotional programs. 

**_ _**  
**_Will your personal information be shared with anyone?_**

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy. As a general rule, we do not disclose specific information about our users to any third parties, save for the purposes set out above. However, in the event that: 

  * you participate in contests or other promotional programs on our site sponsored or organized by third parties;
  * you purchase goods and services offered by third parties or offer goods and services to third parties on our sites;
  * you give us your permission or consent to do so; or 
  * the information in question is publicly-available information, 

your information may be disclosed to and used by such third parties. 

**_Can you change and update your particulars?_**

We encourage you to change or update your particulars, if the same are inaccurate or not updated, and you may do so at [Information Self Updates](http://www.rednano.sg/footer/information_updates.html) page. You will need to have your user id and password.

**_How your data is protected_**

[SPH Search](http://www.sphsearch.sg/) will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal data are protected from unauthorized access. 

Access to your data is password protected. Thus, no other party, including employees of SPH Search, can change the information. However, you must remember to log off from your account and close the browser window after use so that no unauthorized party can have access. You must not, at any time, divulge your password to any third party.

All information gathered by SPH Search is stored in systems that may only be accessed by authorized staff of SPH using assigned user ids and passwords.
